Subtitles by explosiveskull
(WIND BLOWING)
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
(GASPING)
(BIRDS CAWING)
(TOY BEEPING)
(TOY WHIRRING)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(BRANCHES SNAPPING)
(WIND BLOWING)
(RADIO STATIC CRACKLING)
(SIZZLING)
(EXHALES)
REGAN: (WHISPERING) One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(BIRDS SCREECHING
AND FLYING AWAY)
(LOUD CRASHING)
(METAL CREAKING)
(METAL GROANING)
(SHRIEKING)
(EXHALES)
(MOUTHING) I'm sorry.
(RACCOONS CHITTERING)
(SQUEALS)
(FEEDBACK WHINING)
(MUSIC PLAYING
THROUGH HEADPHONES)
? Come a little bit closer
? Hear what I have to say
? Just like children sleeping
? We could dream
this night away
? But there's
a full moon rising
? Let's go
dancing in the light
? We know where
the music's playing
? Let's go out
and feel the night ?
(PUMPING)
(FETAL HEART BEATING)
(LEE SIGHS)
(SOBS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(WHISPERING) Don't worry.
(MUFFLED THUD)
(LIGHT FEEDBACK WHINING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(WHISPERING)
(GASPS)
(EXHALES)
(WATERFALL ROARING)
(HOOTS LOUDLY)
(ALOUD) Hey,
you're all right.
You're all right.
I promise.
(MUFFLED HOOT)
(ALOUD) Why didn't you
let her come?
Do you blame her
for what happened?
No.
Because she
blames herself.
(SNIFFLES)
It was no one's fault.
You still love her, right?
Of course I do.
(NO SOUNDS)
You should tell her.
(FAINT CREAKING)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(SCREAMS)
(RUSTLING)
(CLACKING)
(SNARLING AND GROWLING)
(CREATURE SCREECHING)
(WHIMPERING SOFTLY)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(GROANS)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(SOBBING QUIETLY)
(SHUDDERS)
(CREATURE SCREECHING)
(CLACKING)
(CRASHING)
(STIFLED MOAN)
(EXHALING)
(CLACKING)
(GROWLING AND CLACKING)
(CREAKING)
(SNARLS)
(HISSING AND CLACKING)
(GROWLING)
(CLACKING)
(STIFLED SOB)
(TIMER TICKING)
(TIMER BELL RINGING)
(GROWLING AND SNARLING)
(CREATURE SHRIEKING)
(CLACKING)
(SIGHS)
(STIFLED MOAN)
(SHUDDERING)
- (RUSTLING)
- (GASPS)
(GROWLING)
(NEARBY RUSTLING)
(STIFLED MOANS)
(CLACKING)
(LOUD WHISTLING AND EXPLOSION)
(CREATURE ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
(EXPLOSIONS)
(WHISTLING AND EXPLOSIONS
CONTINUING)
(INHALES)
(EXHALES)
(BABY COOING)
(PANTING)
(BRANCHES SNAPPING)
(CREATURE SCREECHING)
(GROWLING)
(BABY COOING)
(BABY FUSSES)
(BABY CRYING)
(WAILING LOUDLY)
(BABY CONTINUES FUSSING)
- (MUFFLED ROARS OVERHEAD)
- LEE: Shh...
(BABY CONTINUES FUSSING)
(OXYGEN TANK HISSING)
(GROWLING OVERHEAD)
(MUFFLED FUSSING)
(LOUD ROARING)
(CRYING MUFFLED)
(CREATURE SNARLING QUIETLY)
(FEEDBACK WHINING)
(WHINING CONTINUES)
(CREATURE SNARLING)
(CREATURE SCREECHES)
(WHINING STOPS)
- (GASPS)
- LEE: Shh...
(ALOUD) It's okay. It's okay.
You're safe.
They can't hear us.
It worked.
You just need to rest now.
Where are they?
I'll find them.
No, she was with me.
She was with me, and...
And then I had to go
and do laundry, and...
He was with you.
How did he...
Rockets.
So he'd still be there.
- I'm sure he is.
- He knows to wait for you.
And she is...
She's smart. She'll
have found a place.
They know what to do.
(BABY COOING)
It's a boy.
I could've carried him.
He was so heavy,
wasn't he?
I can still...
I can still feel
the weight in my arms.
Small, but
so heavy.
(SOFTLY) And my
hands were free.
I was carrying the bag,
but my hands were free.
You have to stop.
So, I could've
carried him.
I should've carried him.
Who are we
if we can't protect them?
Who are we?
You have to protect them.
Promise me
you will protect them.
(WATER TRICKLING)
(WATER RUNNING)
(SNARLING SOFTLY)
(BABY COOING)
(BABY GURGLES)
(CREATURE HISSING)
(GROWLING)
(CLANGING)
(PANTING)
(GASPING)
(GASPS)
(METAL CREAKING)
(GROWLING)
(ROARING)
(FEEDBACK WHINING)
(ROARING ANGRILY)
(FEEDBACK WHINING CONTINUES)
(PAINED SCREECHING
AND SNARLING)
(CREATURE SHRIEKING)
(SNARLING)
(PANTING)
(DISTANT SNARLING)
(RUSTLING)
(SNARLING)
- Dad!
- (GASPS)
(GROWLING)
(FEEDBACK WHINING)
(WHINING CONTINUES)
(WHINING STOPS)
(SNARLING)
(AX THUDS)
(SCREAMING)
(SNARLING)
(SCREECHING)
(SOBBING QUIETLY)
(ROARING IN DISTANCE)
(CLACKING)
(RUMBLING IN DISTANCE)
(BABY COOING SOFTLY)
(THUDDING)
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
(SNARLING)
(HISSING)
(CLACKING)
(TELEVISION STATIC)
(TELEVISION STATIC CONTINUES)
(SHRIEKS)
(GASPS)
(LOW SNARLING)
(FEEDBACK WHINING)
(FEEDBACK WHINING CONTINUES)
(CREATURE SQUEALING)
(WAILING LOUDLY)
(FEEDBACK AMPLIFIED)
(SCREECHING)
(FEEDBACK STOPS)
(ROARING AND SNARLING)
(FAINT RUMBLING)
(COOING)
Subtitles by explosiveskull